ANDRES GUERRERO

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER / MECHATRONIC ENGINEER

guerrero9510@hotmail.com Medellín, Antioquia, COL (+57) 3174957012 www.portfolio-andresguerrero.vercel.app www.github.com/andresguerrero270895 www.linkedin.com/in/andres-guerrero-00862a217/

Professional Profile

Full Stack Developer with a background as a Mechatronics Engineer. Experience working in Node.js, React, PostgreSQL and WordPress. I am a resilient person, curious, autodidactic, with high capacity to analyze and solve problems, take initiative and teamwork. Knowledge in agile methodologies, GIT, data structure, algorithms and CSS frameworks

Work Experience

Front End Developer WordPress

Digital Marketing - Medellín, Antioquia

- Design landing pages
- Plan advertising campaigns

Agust 2021 - Current

Developer Node.js Freelancer

CorkInc - USA, Remote

- Build API Servers
- Maintain website

March 2022 - September 2022

Educational background

Full Stack Web Developer

Henry - Remote

Technologies: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, NodeJS, Express, React, Redux and PostgreSQL.

February 2022 - September 2022

Degree in Engineer Mechatronic

Institución Universitaria ITM

Technologies: Programming and maintenance of PLC's, management of the TIA PORTAL program.

February 2013 - October 2021

English

SMART Academy

Level: B2 - Upper Intermediate

References

Mark Cornelius O'Leary

Senior Software Engineer en CorkInc

Phone Contact: +57 3008106209

+1 4256501580

Santiago Vanegas Perez

Senior Technician en Endava

Phone Contact: +57 3113907898